(Penny:)You were okay with that?
No. I got upset!
(Leonard:)And Sheldon made me
a beverage, too.
(Penny:)Okay, he just
showed up at my door.
(Penny:)Don't you think
that's a little weird?
(Leonard:)A little, but... he's
basically harmless.
(Leonard:)He's actually kind
of a nice guy.
Okay.
(Penny:)Whatever, look,
my company does not allow me
(Penny:)to socialize with doctors
outside of work.
(Penny:)You got to get rid of him.
(Leonard:)Why am I the one that
has to get rid of him?
I can't do it!
He's my best client!
(Leonard:)All right, I'll
get rid of him.
(Leonard:)But you owe me one.
(Raj:)Hey, we're going to Oliver's
house to see his collection.
(Raj:)You want to go with us?
(Leonard:)Yeah, sure.
(Leonard:)You owe me.
(buzzing, beeping and whirring)
Oh, my God!
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I was wrong.
(Sheldon:)Heaven does exist.
(Sheldon:)And it's in the basement
of a urologist's house
(Sheldon:)in Sherman Oaks.